webnots.com 2019-08-27

# Privacy Policy of webNots.com

Thank you for visiting our web site. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy and the [terms of service](https://www.webnots.com/home/terms-of-service/) before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

  *  __

#### Collection of Information

We collect personally identifiable information, like name, email address, etc., only when voluntarily submitted by visitors. The information you provided is only used to fulfill your specific request, unless you give us permission to use it in another manner, for example to add you to one of our mailing lists.

  *  __

#### Tracking Technology

This site uses Google Analytics as a tracking technology. Google Analytics is useful for gathering information such as browser type, operating system, number of visitors, etc. to this site and understanding how visitors use this site. Tracking is only used to customize the site for visitors and no personal information is collected via Google Analytics or any other tracking technologies.

  *  __

#### Advertisements

Advertisements are shown on this site in order to earn revenue. This helps us to host the site on a paid server and cover all other expenses. We periodically review and block irrelevant ad categories to provide seamless use experience. If you feel the advertisements are disturbing your readability please [contact us](https://www.webnots.com/home/contact-us/) or use ad blockers to block the ad scripts.

  *  __

#### Cookie

Currently we do not use any standalone cookies in this site but we may be using at any point of time in future by changing this privacy policy appropriately. Cookies may present in third party advertisements displayed on this site in order to serve interest based ads.

  *  __

#### Distribution of Information

We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when:

  *  __Permitted or required by law
  *  __Trying to protect actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions
  *  __Investigating fraud which has already taken place.

The information will not be shared with any companies for marketing purposes.

  *  __

#### Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

  *  __

#### Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may [contact us](https://www.webnots.com/home/contact-us/ "Contact Us") with your query or suggestion. Alternatively you can also [drop a mail to us](mailto:contact@webnots.com "Mail to Us").

 __The privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.
